{
    "subject": "resource/Berlin_Oranienburger_Stra\u00dfe_station",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Station",
    "human_readable": "The Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station is a type of Station.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9856278896331787,
            "question": "What type of place is the Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9765686988830566,
            "question": "Is the Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station a building?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9473503232002258,
            "question": "Can you name a characteristic of the Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9359034895896912,
            "question": "Where might you find a Station like the Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8476951122283936,
            "question": "Do you think the Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station is important for people's travel?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8145419955253601,
            "question": "What is the name of the Berlin station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5656157732009888,
            "question": "Are there different types of Stations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4999334216117859,
            "question": "What kind of transportation is likely associated with a Station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.238474503159523,
            "question": "What is another word for 'Station'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2247985601425171,
            "question": "Could you describe what a Station might look like?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station is a type of Station.",
            "html": "dbpedia_850_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is another word for 'Station'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_850_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of transportation is likely associated with a Station?",
            "html": "dbpedia_850_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there different types of Stations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_850_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_850_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_850_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_850_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_850_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_850_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_850_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_850_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_850_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_850_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_850_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents describe Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe as a railway station, which supports the statement that \"The Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station is a type of Station.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The Berlin Oranienburger Stra\u00dfe station is not a type of station, but rather a specific railway station located in the city of Berlin, Germany.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}